<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Awards on Social Science History Association</title>
    <link>https://atkindel.github.io/ssha_web/awards/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Awards on Social Science History Association</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Sun, 30 Jul 2017 13:53:36 -0400</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="https://atkindel.github.io/ssha_web/awards/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Social Science History</title>
      <link>https://atkindel.github.io/ssha_web/awards/founder_prize/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 30 Jul 2017 13:53:36 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://atkindel.github.io/ssha_web/awards/founder_prize/</guid>
      <description>Founder&amp;rsquo;s Prize 2017 Winner: Jaeeun Kim, Contested Embrace: Transborder Membership Politics in Twentieth-Century Korea. (Stanford University Press, 2016)
A beautifully crafted work of historical sociology, Contested Embrace draws on extensive ethnographic and archival research in South Korea, Japan, and Manchuria to challenge the assumption that membership in transborder nations is an ethnodemographic fact. It does so by tracing how the categories of Korean transborder communities were created, and how individuals claimed membership in these categories.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Social Science History</title>
      <link>https://atkindel.github.io/ssha_web/awards/graduate_prize/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 30 Jul 2017 13:53:36 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://atkindel.github.io/ssha_web/awards/graduate_prize/</guid>
      <description> Graduate Student Paper Prize Past Winners    Year &amp;emsp; Author &amp;emsp; Institution &amp;emsp; Title     2016         2015  Francisco J. Beltrán Tapia    “Goths and Vandals” or “Civilized” Farmers?: Common Lands and Agricultural Productivity in Early-Twentieth-Century Spain&amp;rdquo;   2014  Peter B. Owens    The Collective Dynamics of Genocidal Violence in Cambodia, 1975–1979    </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Social Science History</title>
      <link>https://atkindel.github.io/ssha_web/awards/president_award/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 30 Jul 2017 13:53:36 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://atkindel.github.io/ssha_web/awards/president_award/</guid>
      <description>President&amp;rsquo;s Book Award A $1000 prize is awarded annually for a meritorious first work by an early-career scholar. Entrants are judged on scholarly significance, interdisciplinary reach, and methodological innovativeness within monographs analyzing past structures and events and change over time. Books with a copyright date of the previous year that are published within eight years of the author&amp;rsquo;s Ph.D. are eligible for consideration.
Past Winners    Year &amp;emsp; Author &amp;emsp; Institution Title     2016  Jonathan Wyrtzen  Cornell University Making Morocco: Colonial Intervention and the Politics of Identity   2015  Aaron Panofsky  University of Chicago Misbehaving Science: Controversy and the Development of Behavior Genetics   2014  Vanessa Ogle  University of Pennsylvania Contesting Time: The Global Struggle for Uniformity and Its Unintended Consequences, 1870s-1950s   2013  Yiching Wu  University of Toronto The Cultural Revolution at the Margins: Chinese Socialism in Crisis   2012  Lisa Stampniktzky  Harvard Disciplining Terror-How Experts Invented Terrorism   2011  Elizabeth Popp Berman  Berkeley Creating the Market University   2010  Ho-fung Hung  Johns Hopkins Protests with Chinese Characteristics   2009  Greta Krippner  Michigan Capitalizing on Crisis   2008  Anthony Chen  Northwestern The Fifth Freedom   2007  Brody Fischer   For our Poverty of Rights   2007  Issac Martin  Berkeley In Defense of Privilege   2006  Sarah Igo  Vanderbilt The Averaged American: Surveys, Citizens and the Making of a Mass Public   2005  Joseph Gerteis  Minnesota Class and the Color Line   2004  Steven Pfaff  Washington Fight or Flight?</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Social Science History</title>
      <link>https://atkindel.github.io/ssha_web/awards/sharlin_award/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 30 Jul 2017 13:53:36 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://atkindel.github.io/ssha_web/awards/sharlin_award/</guid>
      <description>Allan Sharlin Memorial Book Award A $1,000 prize is awarded annually for an outstanding book in social science history to honor the memory of Allan Sharlin. Allen exemplified the finest traditions of social science history. His training and scholarship were broadly interdisciplinary and he used both quantitative and more traditional methodologies. Books published in the previous year are eligible for consideration.
Past Winners    Year &amp;emsp; Author &amp;emsp; Institution &amp;emsp; Title     2016  Alan L.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>