<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Social Science History Association</title>
    <link>https://atkindel.github.io/ssha_web/</link>
    <description>Recent content on Social Science History Association</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Sun, 30 Jul 2017 13:53:36 -0400</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="https://atkindel.github.io/ssha_web/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>2017 Conference Program</title>
      <link>https://atkindel.github.io/ssha_web/announcement/2017conferenceprogram/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 30 Jul 2017 13:53:36 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://atkindel.github.io/ssha_web/announcement/2017conferenceprogram/</guid>
      <description>Our 2017 annual conference schedule is now available.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>2017 Conference Registration</title>
      <link>https://atkindel.github.io/ssha_web/announcement/2017conferenceregistration/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 30 Jul 2017 13:53:36 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://atkindel.github.io/ssha_web/announcement/2017conferenceregistration/</guid>
      <description>Registration for the 2017 annual conference is now open.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>About SSHA</title>
      <link>https://atkindel.github.io/ssha_web/about/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 30 Jul 2017 13:53:36 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://atkindel.github.io/ssha_web/about/</guid>
      <description>About the Social Science History Association The Social Science History Association was created in 1974 by scholars interested in using social science methods and theories to better understand the past.
The organization might be best seen as a coalition of distinctive scholarly communities which share interests in social life and theory; historiography; and historical and social-scientific methodologies. Our substantive intellectual work ranges from everyday life in the medieval world – and sometimes earlier — to contemporary global politics, but we are united in our historicized approach to understanding human events, explaining social processes, and developing innovative theory.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Annual Conference</title>
      <link>https://atkindel.github.io/ssha_web/conference/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 30 Jul 2017 13:53:36 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://atkindel.github.io/ssha_web/conference/</guid>
      <description>Annual Conference We meet every fall, usually in November. The location changes according to the following logic: once every three years in Chicago, once every three years somewhere on the ‘East Coast’ and once every three years somewhere else. Since 2010, the Association has extended its reach to include Canadian cities as possible locations. The conference involves over a thousand scholars from around the world, although graduate students and faculty from the leading American universities predominant.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Childhood</title>
      <link>https://atkindel.github.io/ssha_web/networks/childhood/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 30 Jul 2017 13:53:36 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://atkindel.github.io/ssha_web/networks/childhood/</guid>
      <description>Childhood and Youth The Childhood &amp;amp; Youth Network of the Social Science History Association brings together scholars from a variety of disciplines who are interested in studying the experiences, ideas, and issues surrounding children, childhood, and youth cultures. The network has recently organized panels on the following themes:
 Child Migrants and Refugees Childhood and Colonialism The Emotional Lives of Children Spaces of Childhood Documenting Histories of Childhood and Youth Schooling and Education Child Labor Children at War Children, Youth, and Political Movements Children and the Environment Youth and Commodification  We invite submissions of papers or (preferably) full panels by February.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Crime, Justice, and the Law</title>
      <link>https://atkindel.github.io/ssha_web/networks/crime/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 30 Jul 2017 13:53:36 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://atkindel.github.io/ssha_web/networks/crime/</guid>
      <description>Crime, Justice, and the Law The Crime, Justice and the Law Network is part of the Social Science History Association (SSHA) and linked with the European Social Science History Conference (ESSHC). The network brings together historians, sociologists, economists, criminologists, geographers, lawyers and independent scholars who are interested in both historical and contemporary developments in crime, policing and the law. The purpose is to provide an international forum for the exchange of ideas and research across disciplines and methodologies.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Culture</title>
      <link>https://atkindel.github.io/ssha_web/networks/culture/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 30 Jul 2017 13:53:36 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://atkindel.github.io/ssha_web/networks/culture/</guid>
      <description>Culture The culture network seeks work exploring culture in two ways. First, we are eager to engage and host discussions of “culture” in its narrower sense, examining forms of entertainment, media, and art as things in themselves alongside the sociological, historical, political, anthropological and economic contexts that explain the appeal, importance, and institutional basis of these expressions across history and around the world. Second, we seek discussions of culture in its much broader sense—the origins, structure, dynamics, and consequences of how people make sense of the world.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Donate to SSHA</title>
      <link>https://atkindel.github.io/ssha_web/donate/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 30 Jul 2017 13:53:36 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://atkindel.github.io/ssha_web/donate/</guid>
      <description>Donate to SSHA Everyone who thinks it is important for the social sciences to be interdisciplinary and to apply social science methods and theories to the past as well as the present has a stake in maintaining the creative legacy of the Social Science History Association. Please consider making a generous tax-deductible donation today!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Economics</title>
      <link>https://atkindel.github.io/ssha_web/networks/economics/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 30 Jul 2017 13:53:36 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://atkindel.github.io/ssha_web/networks/economics/</guid>
      <description>Economics The Economics Network is part of the Social Science History Association (SSHA), and brings together scholars interested in economic history from both economics and history. The Economics network has been an active part of SSHA conferences since the inception of the Association. At the annual conference Economics is generally the primary sponsor of 8-12 sessions, and co-sponsors a similar number each year. There is significant overlap with most of the other networks in SSHA.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Education, Knowledge, and Science</title>
      <link>https://atkindel.github.io/ssha_web/networks/education/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 30 Jul 2017 13:53:36 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://atkindel.github.io/ssha_web/networks/education/</guid>
      <description>Education, Knowledge, and Science The Education/Knowledge/Science (EKS) Network, as one of many parts of the Social Science History Association, brings together scholars across disciplines to the social studies of science, formal education, and processes of knowledge production in broadly historical terms. Current areas of special interest among those within the network include: education and social stratification by race, class, and gender; the history of K-12 and higher education institutions and practices; theoretical bases of social-scientific research; theoretical and methodological engagement between Science &amp;amp; Technology Studies and disciplinary traditions in the social sciences; the politics of expertise; and historical-comparative analyses of science, knowledge, and culture.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Family History and Demography</title>
      <link>https://atkindel.github.io/ssha_web/networks/family/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 30 Jul 2017 13:53:36 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://atkindel.github.io/ssha_web/networks/family/</guid>
      <description>Family History and Demography The Family History and Demography Network of the Social Science History Association calls for papers for a variety of panels that have been proposed by network members, and for proposals for additional panels.
We especially appreciate receiving entire panels, consisting of four papers, with panel chair and commentator, but also invite proposals for roundtables, book sessions, or single papers. The list of panels that have already been proposed appear below.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Health, Medicine, and Body</title>
      <link>https://atkindel.github.io/ssha_web/networks/health/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 30 Jul 2017 13:53:36 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://atkindel.github.io/ssha_web/networks/health/</guid>
      <description>Health, Medicine, and Body The Health, Medicine and Body Network is a group within the Social Science History Association. We are a diverse group of scholars primarily from the fields of anthropology, economics, geography, history, political science, and sociology. Our network usually organizes between eight to ten sessions for the annual meeting of the SSHA, and we co-sponsor a number of additional sessions with other networks such as Criminal Justice and Legal History, Family History and Demography, Labor, Race and Ethnicity, and Women, Gender and Sexuality.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Historical Geography and GIS</title>
      <link>https://atkindel.github.io/ssha_web/networks/geography/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 30 Jul 2017 13:53:36 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://atkindel.github.io/ssha_web/networks/geography/</guid>
      <description>Historical Geography and GIS The Historical Geography and GIS Network focuses on the application of spatial thinking to the study of the past, with a growing focus on GIS-based research. Our papers often take an interdisciplinary approach and incorporate topics such as demography, urban studies, environmental history, migration studies, and health, among others.
Recently proposed sessions: - Building Historical “Big Data” Together: Crowd-sourcing, “Citizen Science” and large-scale online collaboration (Humphrey Southall, humphrey.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Labor</title>
      <link>https://atkindel.github.io/ssha_web/networks/labor/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 30 Jul 2017 13:53:36 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://atkindel.github.io/ssha_web/networks/labor/</guid>
      <description>Labor The Labor Network of the Social Science History Association (SSHA) brings together scholars interested in work, labor, and working-class and labor movements, as they interact with and are formed by class, race, and gender identities and experiences. Engaged in interdisciplinary research, we come from a range of disciplines, including anthropology, economics, history, labor and working-class studies, political science, and sociology. Areas of interest to scholars in the network include but are not limited to comparative and historical perspectives on work; global, national, and local labor movements; class formation and mobilization; inequalities of race, gender, religion, ethnicity, and sexual orientation as they shape work and class organization; informal economies, unfree labor, and precarious work; social movements, unions, and working-class organizations and cultures; immigration and family structures.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Macrohistorical Dynamics</title>
      <link>https://atkindel.github.io/ssha_web/networks/macrohistorical/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 30 Jul 2017 13:53:36 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://atkindel.github.io/ssha_web/networks/macrohistorical/</guid>
      <description>Macrohistorical Dynamics Macrohistorical Dynamics (MHD) is an interdisciplinary social science research community that focuses on questions of large-scale, comparative historical inquiry and the epistemic and theoretical problems that arise at that level of inquiry. The network invites collaboration among historians, social scientists, and philosophers around the conceptual and historiographic problems that arise in large-scale historical inquiry. Contributors to the network have brought perspectives on a wide variety of problem areas, including macro- and historical sociology, world history, Eurasian comparisons, comparative study of civilizations, philosophy of history, globalization, and studies of long-term ecological, technological, demographic, cultural, and political processes.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Migration/Immigration</title>
      <link>https://atkindel.github.io/ssha_web/networks/migration/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 30 Jul 2017 13:53:36 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://atkindel.github.io/ssha_web/networks/migration/</guid>
      <description>Migration/Immigration The Migration/Immigration Network is one of the largest and most active networks at the SSHA. We strongly encourage an interdisciplinary approach to the study of migration and immigration and, as such, our ranks include historians, sociologists, economists, geographers as well as scholars who specialize in ethnic studies, American studies and Latino/a and Chicano/a studies.
Representing one of the largest presences at the SSHA’s annual meetings, members of the network organize panels and roundtables that investigate migration movements within a transnational framework; explore their implications at the local, national and international level; and analyze the impact that the movement of people, goods, and ideas have in a global context.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Politics</title>
      <link>https://atkindel.github.io/ssha_web/networks/politics/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 30 Jul 2017 13:53:36 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://atkindel.github.io/ssha_web/networks/politics/</guid>
      <description>Politics The Politics Network invites scholarship on political development, political institutions, mobilization, contention and conflict. Sessions listed with the Politics Network are frequently cross-listed with other networks, especially States and Society.
In keeping with the traditions of the SSHA we encourage interdisciplinary panels and welcome paper submissions from a wide variety of disciplinary perspectives. While complete panel proposals (at least four papers, a chair, and a discussant) are preferred, we will also do our best to place high-quality individual paper submissions.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Prizes</title>
      <link>https://atkindel.github.io/ssha_web/prizes/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 30 Jul 2017 13:53:36 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://atkindel.github.io/ssha_web/prizes/</guid>
      <description>Book Prizes The Association awards two annual prizes for outstanding books in social science history.
President&amp;rsquo;s Book Award A $1000 prize is awarded annually for a meritorious first work by an early-career scholar. Entrants are judged on scholarly significance, interdisciplinary reach, and methodological innovativeness within monographs analyzing past structures and events and change over time. Books with a copyright date of the previous year that are published within eight years of the author&amp;rsquo;s Ph.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Public Finance</title>
      <link>https://atkindel.github.io/ssha_web/networks/finance/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 30 Jul 2017 13:53:36 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://atkindel.github.io/ssha_web/networks/finance/</guid>
      <description>Public Finance The Public Finance Network invites scholarship the social, political and historical sources and consequences of taxation and other forms of public finance or economic regulation. Sessions listed with the Public Finance Network are often cross-listed with other networks, including Economics and States and Society.
Members of the Public Finance Network come from a variety of academic disciplines, including law, economics, sociology, history, and political science. In keeping with the inherently multidisciplinary nature of the network, and with the traditions of the SSHA, we welcome interdisciplinary panels, and encourage submissions from a wide variety of disciplinary perspectives.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Race and Ethnicity</title>
      <link>https://atkindel.github.io/ssha_web/networks/raceethnicity/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 30 Jul 2017 13:53:36 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://atkindel.github.io/ssha_web/networks/raceethnicity/</guid>
      <description>Race and Ethnicity The Race and Ethnicity Network of the Social Science History Association is a community of scholars who hail from a variety of disciplines, including History, Sociology, Political Science, Geography, area studies, and Anthropology, among others. We employ a wide range of theoretical perspectives to study how race and ethnicity interact with politics, culture, states, institutions, and identities. While a portion of our network members may focus on understanding contemporary processes, we do so with attention to the historical lineages and events that shape them.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Religion</title>
      <link>https://atkindel.github.io/ssha_web/networks/religion/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 30 Jul 2017 13:53:36 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://atkindel.github.io/ssha_web/networks/religion/</guid>
      <description>Religion The SSHA Religion Network is open to all historically oriented scholarship on religion and society. We welcome contributions from historians, sociologists, political scientists, anthropologists, geographers, religious studies scholars, gender and sexuality studies scholars, and those in related fields. Some of the themes typically addressed in network sessions include religion and politics; religion, race, and ethnicity; religion, gender, and sexuality; religion and law; religious nationalism; religion and violence; religion and social movements; religion and state formation; religion and immigration; global religions; conversion and missionary activity; historical patterns of secularization; and secularism.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Rural, Agricultural and Environmental</title>
      <link>https://atkindel.github.io/ssha_web/networks/rural/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 30 Jul 2017 13:53:36 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://atkindel.github.io/ssha_web/networks/rural/</guid>
      <description>Rural, Agricultural and Environmental The Rural, Agricultural and Environmental Network of the Social Science History Association is a broad network including research focused on rural society, on the interaction between rural and urban society, on agricultural history, and on the use of land from an environmental perspective. It rests upon the interdependence between people and land, historically and today, and the effects on humans and nature from this interdependence. Although most panels in recent meetings have addressed these questions focusing on Europe and North America during the last two centuries, panels covering other parts of the world and earlier time periods have also been arranged regularly.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>SSHA Lore and Practices</title>
      <link>https://atkindel.github.io/ssha_web/lore/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 30 Jul 2017 13:53:36 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://atkindel.github.io/ssha_web/lore/</guid>
      <description>Lore and Practices I. Annual Meeting
A. Meeting Date
 Held in the fall, usually in October or November.
 We try to avoid conflicting dates with the Southern Historical Association, Southern Political Science Association, and International Studies Association which usually meet the first week of November, and with the American Anthropological Association, which typically meets late in November.
  B. Site Selection
The Executive Director in conjunction with the Indiana University Conference Boards (IUCB) investigates possible sites for meetings.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>SSHA Officers</title>
      <link>https://atkindel.github.io/ssha_web/officers/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 30 Jul 2017 13:53:36 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://atkindel.github.io/ssha_web/officers/</guid>
      <description>2016-2017 Officers President
Alice Bee Kasakoff
University of South Carolina (Geography)
Vice President
Frederick Wherry
Princeton University (Sociology)
Executive Director
William C. Block
Cornell University (CISER)
Treasurer
Katherine A. Lynch
Carnegie Mellon University (History)
Executive Committee Term Expires 2017
 Rebecca Emigh
UCLA (Sociology)
 Kris Inwood
University of Guelph (Economics and History)
 Ken Sylvester
University of Michigan (ICPSR)
  Term Expires 2018
 Simone Wegge
City University of New York (Economics)</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Social Science History</title>
      <link>https://atkindel.github.io/ssha_web/awards/founder_prize/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 30 Jul 2017 13:53:36 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://atkindel.github.io/ssha_web/awards/founder_prize/</guid>
      <description> Founder&amp;rsquo;s Prize Description goes here.
Past Winners    Year &amp;emsp; Author &amp;emsp; Institution &amp;emsp; Title     2015  Rebecca Jean Emigh, Dylan Riley, Patricia Ahmed    The Racialization of Legal Categories in the First U.S. Census   2014  Andrew Walder    Rebellion and Repression in China, 1966-1971    </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Social Science History</title>
      <link>https://atkindel.github.io/ssha_web/awards/graduate_prize/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 30 Jul 2017 13:53:36 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://atkindel.github.io/ssha_web/awards/graduate_prize/</guid>
      <description> Graduate Student Paper Prize Description goes here.
Past Winners    Year &amp;emsp; Author &amp;emsp; Institution &amp;emsp; Title     2015  Francisco J. Beltrán Tapia    “Goths and Vandals” or “Civilized” Farmers?: Common Lands and Agricultural Productivity in Early-Twentieth-Century Spain&amp;rdquo;   2014  Peter B. Owens    The Collective Dynamics of Genocidal Violence in Cambodia, 1975–1979    </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Social Science History</title>
      <link>https://atkindel.github.io/ssha_web/awards/president_award/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 30 Jul 2017 13:53:36 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://atkindel.github.io/ssha_web/awards/president_award/</guid>
      <description>President&amp;rsquo;s Book Award A $1000 prize is awarded annually for a meritorious first work by an early-career scholar. Entrants are judged on scholarly significance, interdisciplinary reach, and methodological innovativeness within monographs analyzing past structures and events and change over time. Books with a copyright date of the previous year that are published within eight years of the author&amp;rsquo;s Ph.D. are eligible for consideration.
Past Winners    Year &amp;emsp; Author &amp;emsp; Institution Title     2016  Jonathan Wyrtzen  Cornell University Making Morocco: Colonial Intervention and the Politics of Identity   2015  Aaron Panofsky  University of Chicago Misbehaving Science: Controversy and the Development of Behavior Genetics   2014  Vanessa Ogle  University of Pennsylvania Contesting Time: The Global Struggle for Uniformity and Its Unintended Consequences, 1870s-1950s   2013  Yiching Wu  University of Toronto The Cultural Revolution at the Margins: Chinese Socialism in Crisis   2012  Lisa Stampniktzky  Harvard Disciplining Terror-How Experts Invented Terrorism   2011  Elizabeth Popp Berman  Berkeley Creating the Market University   2010  Ho-fung Hung  Johns Hopkins Protests with Chinese Characteristics   2009  Greta Krippner  Michigan Capitalizing on Crisis   2008  Anthony Chen  Northwestern The Fifth Freedom   2007  Brody Fischer   For our Poverty of Rights   2007  Issac Martin  Berkeley In Defense of Privilege   2006  Sarah Igo  Vanderbilt The Averaged American: Surveys, Citizens and the Making of a Mass Public   2005  Joseph Gerteis  Minnesota Class and the Color Line   2004  Steven Pfaff  Washington Fight or Flight?</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Social Science History</title>
      <link>https://atkindel.github.io/ssha_web/awards/sharlin_award/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 30 Jul 2017 13:53:36 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://atkindel.github.io/ssha_web/awards/sharlin_award/</guid>
      <description>Allan Sharlin Memorial Book Award A $1,000 prize is awarded annually for an outstanding book in social science history to honor the memory of Allan Sharlin. Allen exemplified the finest traditions of social science history. His training and scholarship were broadly interdisciplinary and he used both quantitative and more traditional methodologies. Books published in the previous year are eligible for consideration.
Past Winners    Year &amp;emsp; Author &amp;emsp; Institution &amp;emsp; Title     2016  Alan L.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Social Science History</title>
      <link>https://atkindel.github.io/ssha_web/journal/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 30 Jul 2017 13:53:36 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://atkindel.github.io/ssha_web/journal/</guid>
      <description>Social Science History Social Science History is dedicated to the study of social theory within an empirical historical context. Our interdisciplinary readership includes anthropologists, demographers, economists, geographers, historians, political scientists, and sociologists, all in pursuit of a deep understanding of societies, past and present. The journal invites articles that blend empirical research with theoretical work, undertake comparisons across time and space, or contribute to the development of quantitative and qualitative methods of analysis.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>States and Society</title>
      <link>https://atkindel.github.io/ssha_web/networks/states/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 30 Jul 2017 13:53:36 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://atkindel.github.io/ssha_web/networks/states/</guid>
      <description>States and Society The States and Society Network invites scholarship on state-building, social change, social conflict, political institutions, and social development, among other topics.
The submission deadline for 2018 is March 1, 2018; submissions can be made via the following link: http://prd.sshaconference.org/. This year the States and Society network is also interested in works on the following topics (generated by the participants at our network meeting in 2016 and 2017!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Urban</title>
      <link>https://atkindel.github.io/ssha_web/networks/urban/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 30 Jul 2017 13:53:36 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://atkindel.github.io/ssha_web/networks/urban/</guid>
      <description>Urban The Urban network endeavors to bring social scientific and historical modes of analysis to the urban form. We are interested in the historical trajectory of the city, the spatial forms linked to the urban life, social arrangements, governance and politics, the specificity of urban economics, cultural forms that emerge and thrive in cities, urban institutions, place identities, real and imagined urban forms, and the historical trajectory of specifically urban phenomena across regional, temporal, and cultural categories.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Women, Gender and Sexuality</title>
      <link>https://atkindel.github.io/ssha_web/networks/gendersexuality/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 30 Jul 2017 13:53:36 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://atkindel.github.io/ssha_web/networks/gendersexuality/</guid>
      <description>Women, Gender and Sexuality Who we are:
The Women, Gender, and Sexuality Network of the SSHA seeks to inspire interdisciplinary collaboration among scholars interested in the study of women, men, gender, and sexuality around the world. WGS network members are excited to increase the reach of our very active network through papers and panels – often collaborating with other SSHA networks. We work with scholars who focus on feminist, queer and intersectional approaches to the study of power, the body, identities, the law, policy, social movements, migration, spaces, language, intimacies, etc.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>