<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Social Science History Association</title>
    <link>https://atkindel.github.io/ssha_web/</link>
    <description>Recent content on Social Science History Association</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Sun, 30 Jul 2017 13:53:36 -0400</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="https://atkindel.github.io/ssha_web/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>About SSHA</title>
      <link>https://atkindel.github.io/ssha_web/about/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 30 Jul 2017 13:53:36 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://atkindel.github.io/ssha_web/about/</guid>
      <description>About the Social Science History Association The Social Science History Association is an interdisciplinary organization that publishes its own journal, Social Science History, organizes an annual conference, supports graduate student travel to the conference, and awards book prizes. With scholars from history, economics, sociology, demography, anthropology, and other social sciences, the association brings together scholars in thematic networks where they can explore common questions. Each network organizes its own call for papers and selects the bulk of the papers to be presented at the annual conference.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Annual Conference</title>
      <link>https://atkindel.github.io/ssha_web/conference/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 30 Jul 2017 13:53:36 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://atkindel.github.io/ssha_web/conference/</guid>
      <description>Annual Conference We meet every fall, usually in November. The location changes according to the following logic: once every three years in Chicago, once every three years somewhere on the ‘East Coast’ and once every three years somewhere else. Since 2010, the Association has extended its reach to include Canadian cities as possible locations. The conference involves over a thousand scholars from around the world, although graduate students and faculty from the leading American universities predominant.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Donate to SSHA</title>
      <link>https://atkindel.github.io/ssha_web/donate/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 30 Jul 2017 13:53:36 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://atkindel.github.io/ssha_web/donate/</guid>
      <description>Donate to SSHA Everyone who thinks it is important for the social sciences to be interdisciplinary and to apply social science methods and theories to the past as well as the present has a stake in maintaining the creative legacy of the Social Science History Association. Please consider making a generous tax-deductible donation today!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Networks</title>
      <link>https://atkindel.github.io/ssha_web/network/crime/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 30 Jul 2017 13:53:36 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://atkindel.github.io/ssha_web/network/crime/</guid>
      <description>SSHA Networks With scholars from history, economics, sociology, demography, anthropology, and other social sciences, the association brings together scholars in thematic networks where they can explore common questions. Each network organizes its own call for papers and selects the bulk of the papers to be presented at the annual conference. This open, flexible, and non-hierarchical structure makes these networks particularly welcoming spaces for younger scholars and invigorating tonic for older academics.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Networks</title>
      <link>https://atkindel.github.io/ssha_web/network/migration/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 30 Jul 2017 13:53:36 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://atkindel.github.io/ssha_web/network/migration/</guid>
      <description>SSHA Networks With scholars from history, economics, sociology, demography, anthropology, and other social sciences, the association brings together scholars in thematic networks where they can explore common questions. Each network organizes its own call for papers and selects the bulk of the papers to be presented at the annual conference. This open, flexible, and non-hierarchical structure makes these networks particularly welcoming spaces for younger scholars and invigorating tonic for older academics.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Networks</title>
      <link>https://atkindel.github.io/ssha_web/networks/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 30 Jul 2017 13:53:36 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://atkindel.github.io/ssha_web/networks/</guid>
      <description>SSHA Networks With scholars from history, economics, sociology, demography, anthropology, and other social sciences, the association brings together scholars in thematic networks where they can explore common questions. Each network organizes its own call for papers and selects the bulk of the papers to be presented at the annual conference. This open, flexible, and non-hierarchical structure makes these networks particularly welcoming spaces for younger scholars and invigorating tonic for older academics.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Prizes</title>
      <link>https://atkindel.github.io/ssha_web/prizes/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 30 Jul 2017 13:53:36 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://atkindel.github.io/ssha_web/prizes/</guid>
      <description>Book Prizes The Association awards two annual prizes for outstanding books in social science history.
President&amp;rsquo;s Book Award A $1000 prize is awarded annually for a meritorious first work by an early-career scholar. Entrants are judged on scholarly significance, interdisciplinary reach, and methodological innovativeness within monographs analyzing past structures and events and change over time. Books with a copyright date of the previous year that are published within eight years of the author&amp;rsquo;s Ph.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Social Science History</title>
      <link>https://atkindel.github.io/ssha_web/awards/founder_prize/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 30 Jul 2017 13:53:36 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://atkindel.github.io/ssha_web/awards/founder_prize/</guid>
      <description> Founder&amp;rsquo;s Prize Description goes here.
Past Winners    Year &amp;emsp; Author &amp;emsp; Institution &amp;emsp; Title     2015  Rebecca Jean Emigh, Dylan Riley, Patricia Ahmed    The Racialization of Legal Categories in the First U.S. Census   2014  Andrew Walder    Rebellion and Repression in China, 1966-1971    </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Social Science History</title>
      <link>https://atkindel.github.io/ssha_web/awards/graduate_prize/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 30 Jul 2017 13:53:36 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://atkindel.github.io/ssha_web/awards/graduate_prize/</guid>
      <description> Graduate Student Paper Prize Description goes here.
Past Winners    Year &amp;emsp; Author &amp;emsp; Institution &amp;emsp; Title     2015  Francisco J. Beltrán Tapia    “Goths and Vandals” or “Civilized” Farmers?: Common Lands and Agricultural Productivity in Early-Twentieth-Century Spain&amp;rdquo;   2014  Peter B. Owens    The Collective Dynamics of Genocidal Violence in Cambodia, 1975–1979    </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Social Science History</title>
      <link>https://atkindel.github.io/ssha_web/awards/president_award/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 30 Jul 2017 13:53:36 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://atkindel.github.io/ssha_web/awards/president_award/</guid>
      <description>President&amp;rsquo;s Book Award A $1000 prize is awarded annually for a meritorious first work by an early-career scholar. Entrants are judged on scholarly significance, interdisciplinary reach, and methodological innovativeness within monographs analyzing past structures and events and change over time. Books with a copyright date of the previous year that are published within eight years of the author&amp;rsquo;s Ph.D. are eligible for consideration.
Past Winners    Year &amp;emsp; Author &amp;emsp; Institution Title     2016  Jonathan Wyrtzen  Cornell University Making Morocco: Colonial Intervention and the Politics of Identity   2015  Aaron Panofsky  University of Chicago Misbehaving Science: Controversy and the Development of Behavior Genetics   2014  Vanessa Ogle  University of Pennsylvania Contesting Time: The Global Struggle for Uniformity and Its Unintended Consequences, 1870s-1950s   2013  Yiching Wu  University of Toronto The Cultural Revolution at the Margins: Chinese Socialism in Crisis   2012  Lisa Stampniktzky  Harvard Disciplining Terror-How Experts Invented Terrorism   2011  Elizabeth Popp Berman  Berkeley Creating the Market University   2010  Ho-fung Hung  Johns Hopkins Protests with Chinese Characteristics   2009  Greta Krippner  Michigan Capitalizing on Crisis   2008  Anthony Chen  Northwestern The Fifth Freedom   2007  Brody Fischer   For our Poverty of Rights   2007  Issac Martin  Berkeley In Defense of Privilege   2006  Sarah Igo  Vanderbilt The Averaged American: Surveys, Citizens and the Making of a Mass Public   2005  Joseph Gerteis  Minnesota Class and the Color Line   2004  Steven Pfaff  Washington Fight or Flight?</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Social Science History</title>
      <link>https://atkindel.github.io/ssha_web/awards/sharlin_award/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 30 Jul 2017 13:53:36 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://atkindel.github.io/ssha_web/awards/sharlin_award/</guid>
      <description>Allan Sharlin Memorial Book Award A $1,000 prize is awarded annually for an outstanding book in social science history to honor the memory of Allan Sharlin. Allen exemplified the finest traditions of social science history. His training and scholarship were broadly interdisciplinary and he used both quantitative and more traditional methodologies. Books published in the previous year are eligible for consideration.
Past Winners    Year &amp;emsp; Author &amp;emsp; Institution &amp;emsp; Title     2016  Alan L.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Social Science History</title>
      <link>https://atkindel.github.io/ssha_web/journal/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 30 Jul 2017 13:53:36 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://atkindel.github.io/ssha_web/journal/</guid>
      <description>Social Science History Social Science History is dedicated to the study of social theory within an empirical historical context. Our interdisciplinary readership includes anthropologists, demographers, economists, geographers, historians, political scientists, and sociologists, all in pursuit of a deep understanding of societies, past and present. The journal invites articles that blend empirical research with theoretical work, undertake comparisons across time and space, or contribute to the development of quantitative and qualitative methods of analysis.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>